I'm trying to platinum every game I own.
We're still making our way through every
single COD. And our last COD was Modern
Warfare 3, which unfortunately means
it's time
[Music]
for Released in 2013. Developed by
Infinity Ward, Call of Duty Ghosts is
one of the most hated CODs of all time.
Now, is it actually that bad or was it
just an impossible task to follow up
what was Black Ops 2 while also moving
to the next generation of consoles?
Well, going for the 51 campaign,
survival and weird zombies game mode
trophies might help us decide, but I'm
going into this one with a little bit of
bias, but launching head first into the
veteran campaign, which of course we
need to play to get the veteran trophy.
You've earned it. We got our first
trophy very quickly. Spatial awareness
for getting our first ke of the
campaign. Ooh, spatial awareness got his
ass. And we not only get a trophy for
getting our first ke, but we also get
the trophy ghost stories for completing
the first mission where a massive nuke
space station gets hij and starts
dropping censored on A. And while the